Finding Aid for David Noel Freedman Papers 1932-1982
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Michigan Quarterly Review 1982-1983
  - Correspondence
    - Weiss, Theodore (Box 10)
- Correspondence 1955-1979
  The Correspondence Series, 1955-1979 consists of correspondence between Freedman and the author indicated by the folder title and touches on several topics. Many of the individuals listed worked with Freedman on various projects. The folders are arranged alphabetically by last name.
  - Bailey, John (Box 10)
  - Campbell, E. F, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - [Campbell, E. F., Biblical Archaeologist Reader] (Box 10)
  - Dilella, Alexander, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Greenfield, Jonas C. (Box 10)
  - Harrelson, Walter (Box 10)
  - Hartman, Louis F., 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Hillers, Del (Box 10)
  - Moore, Carey (Box 10)
  - Myers, Jacob (Box 10)
  - Pope, Marvin (Box 10)
  - Radday, Yehuda (Box 10)
  - Speiser, E. A. (Box 10)